How are you feeling today?
你今天感觉怎么样？
I've got a few aches and pains but nothing serious.
我有点疼痛不适，但并不严重。
However, when things become more critical I would normally book myself an appointment with my GP — although by the time I get to see him, the problem will have probably gone away.
然而，当情况变得更危急时，我通常会给自己预约家庭医生——不过等我见到他的时候，问题可能已经不存在了。
That's because in the UK at least, we usually have to wait a few days before the doctor can fit us in and then when we're at the surgery, we have a long wait.
这是因为至少在英国，我们通常得等上几天医生才能安排时间见我们，而当我们到了诊所，还得等很久。
Luckily today, technology has come to our rescue.
幸运的是，如今科技拯救了我们。
There are thousands of apps available on our smartphones that can offer first aid advice and allow us to self-diagnose our ailments — ranging from a simple cold or flu to some exotic disease such as dengue fever.
我们的智能手机上有成千上万的应用程序，可以提供急救建议，还能让我们自我诊断自己的疾病——从简单的感冒或流感到像登革热这样的异国疾病。
And together with the internet, we have a whole encyclopedia of medical information at our fingertips.
再加上互联网，我们触手可及一整套医学信息百科全书。
But is this just what the doctor ordered?
但这真的是医生们想要的吗？
Is too much knowledge a good thing?
知道得太多是件好事吗？
By reading up on an illness, we discover its side-effects and what could happen in a worst-case situation.
通过查阅有关疾病的资料，我们会发现它的副作用以及在最糟糕的情况下可能会发生什么。
More worrying is that we give ourselves the wrong diagnosis, and then worry ourselves sick that we're going to die.
更令人担忧的是，我们会给自己做出错误的诊断，然后担心自己会病死。
This health anxiety fuelled by the internet, is called cyberchondria.
这种由互联网加剧产生的健康焦虑被称为“网络疑病症”。
It gives sufferers a deep fear of diseases and, according to experts, it's on the rise.
它让患者对疾病深感恐惧，而且据专家称，这种情况正在增加。
Professor Peter Tyrer from Imperial College London, told the BBC: "We find that approximately four out of five of our patients with health anxiety spend literally hours on the internet.... one of the first things we do in treatment is we tell them to stop browsing the internet."
伦敦帝国理工学院的彼得·泰勒教授告诉BBC：“我们发现，大约五分之四的有健康焦虑的患者实际上会在互联网上花费数小时......我们治疗时首先要做的事情之一就是告诉他们停止浏览互联网。”
Of course there is no doubt, the world wide web has most of the information we need to diagnose our symptoms but Doctor Tyrer points out "it doesn't have any judgement associated with it."
当然，毫无疑问，万维网拥有我们诊断症状所需的大部分信息，但泰勒医生指出：“它没有任何相关的判断力。”
This is why having a consultation with a doctor face-to-face still has its benefits, although a study a few years ago found many GPs felt intimidated by the increasing numbers of web-wise patients arriving in surgeries.
这就是为什么与医生面对面咨询仍然有其好处，尽管几年前的一项研究发现，许多家庭医生对越来越多熟悉网络的患者到诊所就诊感到不安。
One doctor admitted to not being very happy about patients using the internet, saying: "They all seemed to come to me with things I'd never heard of and very often with things which seem rather bizarre or inappropriate."
一位医生承认对患者使用互联网不太满意，他说：“他们来找我的时候，似乎都带着一些我从未听说过的东西，而且很多时候是一些看起来相当奇怪或不合适的东西。”
But Professor Sue Ziebland, from Oxford University, has spent 15 years examining how patients use the internet - including people with cancer.
但是牛津大学的苏·齐布兰德教授花了15年时间研究患者如何使用互联网，包括癌症患者。
She found that doctors now routinely discuss it as a resource with patients during consultations so it becomes an everyday part of medical conversation.
她发现，医生现在在会诊时，会经常地与患者讨论互联网作为一种信息来源的问题，所以它已经成为医疗对话中日常的一部分。
It would seem then that a virtual online doctor can prescribe a dose of useful advice but technology hasn't replaced the human medical expert just yet.
这样看来，虚拟的在线医生可以给出一份有用的建议，但科技还没有完全取代人类医学专家。